All right.
好的。
So we've done variations and you can use that exercise anytime to improve your English skills.
所以我们做了一些变化，您可以随时使用该练习来提高您的英语技能。
Now we're going to go onto an exercise that I designed specifically to improve your ability to think
现在我们要进行一个我专门设计的练习来提高你的思考能力
in English.
用英语讲。
Now if you've already seen this in my other course about learning to think in English the English brain
现在，如果你已经在我的另一门关于学习用英语思考的课程中看到了这一点，那就是英语大脑
course then I'm sorry.
当然，我很抱歉。
I want to cover it in this course because I think it's so important and a lot of students have told
我想在本课程中介绍它，因为我认为它非常重要，而且很多学生都告诉过
me how useful it is to them.
我对他们有多大用处。
So I want to make sure that we included in this course so that you can use it to actually start thinking
所以我想确保我们包含在这门课程中，这样你就可以用它来真正开始思考
in English thinking in English is very important.
in English 用英语思考是很重要的。
If you can start thinking in English then you can start speaking in English more naturally.
如果您可以开始用英语思考，那么您可以更自然地开始说英语。
You don't have to translate in your head.
您不必在脑海中翻译。
All right.
好的。
So this is very simple.
所以这很简单。
Let me explain how we do it.
让我解释一下我们是如何做到的。
All right.
好的。
So the forward exercise is going to force us to use English very flexibly very creatively.
因此，前向练习将迫使我们非常灵活、非常有创意地使用英语。
We have no choice but to think in English to do this.
我们别无选择，只能用英语思考来做到这一点。
Choose four words.
选择四个字。
And once you get good you can use five maybe six.
一旦你变得好起来，你可以使用五个或者六个。
And I recommend using different forms of words.
我建议使用不同形式的单词。
So don't use only verbs maybe use a verb.
所以不要只使用动词可能使用动词。
Use an adjective.
使用形容词。
Use another verb use a noun different types.
使用另一个动词使用不同类型的名词。
And it's good if you choose words that can have many different forms like cooler coolest cool right.
如果您选择可以具有多种不同形式的单词，例如coolest coolest cool right，那就太好了。
Because cool has different meanings too.
因为cool也有不同的含义。
That's good.
那挺好的。
Don't put each word into its own sentence.
不要将每个单词放在自己的句子中。
They all have to be in one sentence.
它们都必须在一个句子中。
You can move them around in any order you like.
您可以按照您喜欢的任何顺序移动它们。
Doesn't matter what order they're in.
不管他们的顺序是什么。
That's fine.
没关系。
In fact you should be moving them around and trying them in different ways.
事实上，你应该移动它们并以不同的方式尝试它们。
You can explore the different meanings of each word.
您可以探索每个单词的不同含义。
As I mentioned cool means like you're or you're an awesome person.
正如我提到的，酷意味着你是或者你是一个了不起的人。
And it also means kind of cold.
它也意味着有点冷。
OK.
好的。
But also you can change the forms.
但您也可以更改表格。
So for example think we can say thankful.
因此，例如认为我们可以说感谢。
Thanks.
谢谢。
There are lots of different forms of words as well.
还有很多不同形式的词。
So one sentence not two sentences very important that you make it fit in one sentence that forces you
所以一句话不是两句话非常重要，你让它适合一个迫使你的句子
to be very creative.
要非常有创意。
OK.
好的。
Any order any form.
任何订单任何形式。
Now I've decided to use for this one.
现在我决定用这个。
We're going to use communicate and turn and fool and cost.
我们将使用通信、转向、傻瓜和成本。
And honestly when I was working on this class plan I just chose four words.
老实说，当我制定这个班级计划时，我只选择了四个词。
I chose the first four words I thought of.
我选择了我想到的前四个词。
There's nothing special about these words.
这些话没有什么特别之处。
If you want to change them and choose different words you should.
如果您想更改它们并选择不同的单词，您应该这样做。
And all you have to do to do this exercise is sit down write forwards down and then see how many different
做这个练习你所要做的就是坐下来写下然后看看有多少不同
sentences you can come up with and how many different meanings you can come up with.
你能想出的句子和你能想出多少不同的意思。
Let's look at two ways that we can use communicate turn fool and cost.
让我们看一下我们可以使用通信变成傻瓜和成本的两种方式。
I'm going to give two examples but there are many many other ways we can use these words to make a sentence.
我将举两个例子，但还有很多其他方法可以使用这些词来造句。
Just before we do let me go over a couple of the different forms so we could have communicate.
就在我们这样做之前，让我回顾一下几种不同的表格，以便我们可以进行交流。
We could have communication.
我们可以进行交流。
We could have communicator right.
我们可以有沟通的权利。
We could have a couple of different forms of communicate turn turning turns.
我们可以有几种不同形式的交流转弯转弯。
OK.
好的。
Those are OK.
这些都可以。
Fool foolish Fool are fools.
傻瓜傻傻傻傻。
OK.
好的。
We can use those cost costs sometimes costing.
我们可以使用这些成本成本有时成本。
So let's let's look at a couple of examples sentences.
所以让我们看几个例句。
Number one the cost of a failure to communicate.
第一是沟通失败的代价。
Whose turn it is to speak might result in someone looking foolish.
轮到谁说话可能会导致某人看起来很愚蠢。
OK.
好的。
So we have communicate in its original form the one we have here.
因此，我们以原始形式进行了交流，就像我们在这里所拥有的那样。
This turn doesn't mean turn left or right but in order.
这个转弯不是指左转或右转，而是按顺序。
Whose turn is it.
该轮到谁啦。
It's my turn.
轮到我了。
OK then we have foolish foolish which is one form of the word fool and we have cost in its original
好的，那么我们有愚蠢的愚蠢，这是傻瓜这个词的一种形式，我们在其原始版本中付出了代价
form.
形式。
OK.
好的。
Let's see if we can come up with one which is very different.
让我们看看我们是否能想出一个非常不同的方案。
Next one I foolishly turned onto the wrong road because of miscommunication and it cost me a job.
下一个我因为沟通不畅而愚蠢地走错了路，这让我失去了一份工作。
So do we have cost.
我们也有成本。
Yes.
是的。
This one we've used the verb form miscommunication.
这个我们使用了动词形式miscommunication。
Well OK.
好吧。
That's a form of communicate miscommunication is a noun.
那是一种沟通形式，沟通不畅是一个名词。
OK.
好的。
We've used it as a noun full.
我们把它用作名词full。
We've used foolishly foolishly.
我们愚蠢地愚蠢地使用。
This is an adverb used an adverb foolishly turned and turned in the past tense past past tense we've
This is a adverb used a adverbly turn and turn in过去式过去过去式我们已经
used turned.
用过。
So we've got all four of our words full cost turn and communicate.
因此，我们已经将所有四个单词全部转换并进行了交流。
But we've used them very differently than the previous one.
但是我们使用它们的方式与之前的非常不同。
And we could keep going.
我们可以继续前进。
I don't want to bore you with many many examples but I hope this gets the idea across.
我不想用很多例子让你厌烦，但我希望这能让你明白这一点。
Nothing special about the words you have to force yourself to stick with the rules follow the rules
你必须强迫自己遵守规则的话并没有什么特别之处 遵守规则
no more than one sentence.
不超过一句话。
Once you get good at it try five words try six words and it's very important that it actually makes
一旦你擅长它尝试五个词尝试六个词，它实际上是非常重要的
sense.
感觉。
It can't just fit together.
它不能只是结合在一起。
Dramatic and you say all the grammar is right.
戏剧性的，你说所有的语法都是正确的。
It also has to make sense.
它也必须有意义。
It has to be logical.
它必须是合乎逻辑的。
It has to be something that you could hear in a story if it's grammatically correct and you've just
它必须是你可以在故事中听到的东西，如果它在语法上是正确的并且你刚刚
got a bunch of.
有一堆。
And then and then and then and then.
然后，然后，然后，然后。
And the sentence is this long.
而且句子就是这么长。
You failed.
你失败了。
It's got to be a nice neat clean sentence.
这必须是一个漂亮整洁干净的句子。
OK.
好的。
You've got to follow the rules.
你必须遵守规则。